{
    "id": "8fa41997d9c845f2aff3511e6b606216",
    "title": "Both, either, neither | grammar exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "8557916306384b53b0a487a2f32fea91",
            "title": "Both, Either And Neither",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "…………….. my sisters live in the US.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Both",
                        "Either",
                        "Neither"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "……………….. of them were ill and didn’t go to work.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Both",
                        "Either",
                        "Neither"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I know you don’t like me. I don’t like you ………………….",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "both",
                        "either",
                        "neither"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "John didn’t come. …………….. did Peter.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Both",
                        "Either",
                        "Neither"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I don’t like ………………… of these colors.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "either",
                        "neither",
                        "both"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I can’t decide between these two dresses. I like them …………………",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "both",
                        "either",
                        "neither"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "……………… cheese or butter will do.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Either",
                        "Neither",
                        "Both"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We can ……………….. swim.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "both",
                        "either",
                        "neither"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………. of them is here.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Both",
                        "Either",
                        "Neither"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I don’t like ……………….. of them.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "either",
                        "neither",
                        "both"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}